

PALINA LIAMESHCHANKA

BUSINESS ANALYST

ENGLISH: B2 POLISH: C1 GERMAN: A2

BELARUSSIAN: NATIVE

RUSSIAN: NATIVE

CONTACT INFO



+48787302312



lemeshch2000@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/palinaliameschanka-651026177



Krakow, Poland Citizenship: Poland

HARD SKILLS

Jira

MS Office

Postman

Confluence

Miro

SQL

Draw.io

Figma

CMS AEM

Whimsical

WORK SKILLS

- · Analytical and Critical Thinking
- Understanding the Business Objective
- Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- · Requirements Elicitation
- Processes Modeling (UML, BPMN)
- Software Development Methodologies
- Adobe Experience Manager
- Risk Management
- Understanding Of Databases
- Facilitation Skills

ABOUT ME

Business Analyst with over 3 years of experience in IT sphere. Deep understanding of project life-cycle principles, requirements elicitation, clarification, documenting, modelling and creating prototypes. Able to communicate confidently with stakeholders to gather information about their needs and preferences. Possess analytical and critical thinking. High level of self-motivation and selfeducation.

EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst

March 2021 — October 2024

Company: Andersen

Industries: Banking, Enterprises, Insurance,

Investment & Trading, Engineering

- Gathering, validating and documenting business requirements.
- Creation of prototypes using Figma to ensure alignment between business needs and technical specifications.
- Development of the project documentation (Confluence).
- Modeling business processes and identifying opportunities for process improvements (via UML and BPMN notations), specifically optimizing operational workflows for engineering project.
- Content management via AEM for insurance industry.
- Process modeling and workflow enhancement for industrial application.
- Development and optimization of Pumps and Cyclones simulation programs for engineering processes.

Service Sales Manager

May 2020 — January 2021

Company: OHI-s

• Sales of Specialized Courses: Drove a 35% increase in enrollments for educational courses tailored to dental professionals in Englishspeaking markets.

EDUCATION

Interpreter

2017-2022

University: Minsk State Linguistic University

Learning Confluence and Jira

2021

LinkedIn Learning

Description of processes in BP

2022

Udemy

FinTech - Investments

Internal course in Andersen

SQL for Business Analysis

2023

Udemy

SA for Intermediates

2024

Internal course

I agree to the processing by the advertiser of my personal data contained in my job offer for the purposes necessary for the implementation of the recruitment process following the act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data (i.e. Journal of Laws of 2016, item 922).

At the same time, I agree with the processing of my data by the advertiser for future recruitment within 6 months from the date of opening the CV.

A work permit is not required.